[{"answer": "What for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Isn't putting this guy's picture on your desk a little transparent", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " my friend, I feel a cold coming on. Could you get me a cold pill from the medicine cabinet", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes, yes, I'll check with the pharmacist", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Ah they don't know a darn thing. That's why my flight the that place's been delayed. They're all morons. Matter of fact, I'll bet you that that flight to that place takes off before my flight to that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Friendly wager", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "This could be that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Come on, that place City", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "C'mon that place, let's go", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "that place, yeah", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "I don't care, why are you telling me this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Why would I freak out?  Pilot..", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh, it doesn't matter now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yeah, you're on top of it, and I'm on the bottom", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, Mr. my friend, looks like you're in the hole", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "All right, but I wanna see some cash on the table", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "We've been betting on arrivals and departures.  But I'm down", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Sure you do", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "But someone is waiting for me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I'm freakin' out! I am freakin' out", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I'm freakin' out! I am freakin' out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Which one do you think I want", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend, I think", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Yeah, he was nice", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "my friend... Yeah, he was a nice guy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What company was it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "That's at the airport, right", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "All right, all right. You sound a little freaked out yourself", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Right, I don't want my friend to think I stood her up. I'll never get another date with her. She'll freak out", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I am a little freaked out", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Okay, that place, we're back in business. Let's check out the board. Now, who do you like", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "All right, I'll give you a sportin' chance. I'll take that place", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "All right, I'll give you a sportin' chance. I'll take that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Double or nothin'", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "my friend? Yes, I suppose he is white. You know, I never really thought about it. I don't see people in terms of color. You know, there's someone I'd like you to meet. Hand on...  Is Mr. my friend in", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Diplomat_s-Club.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "He left... huh... my friend, you hungry", "qsentId": 36}]